- Previously on
"The Bachelorette"...
- She doesn't trust me.
Please go up there
and tell her the truth.
- Yeah, I plan on it.
Luke S. came up to me
asking me to put in
a good word for him.
- I'm confused
but also, like, irritated.
I just, like, don't know
who to trust.
- I said go tell her the truth
and say that you lied.
- No, no, no.
- You are a liar.
- My mind feels like mush.
The drama is stressing me out.
- I'm not talking bad
about Luke S.
- You literally--
you smeared him.
You smeared him.
You're a liar.
- It's not a secret.
None of us care for Luke P.
- Just don't cross
the line anymore
'cause you don't want
to do that, I promise.
- I'm very conflicted.
Hey.
I really like Luke P.,
but there are red flags
everywhere.
The guys don't like you.
Like, I just don't understand.
- It's really not adding up.
Anywhere I've ever been
in my whole life,
everyone loves me.
- Luke stresses me
because I want
so much more out of him
than he's giving me.
I don't want to be married
to somebody who thinks
that it's everybody else's
fault and can't take ownership.
I want to know who you are,
and I don't.
Luke, I can't
give you this rose.
[dramatic music]
- What happens next?
Find out tonight.
- What do you think
went down today?
We haven't seen Luke yet,
so honestly hopefully
we won't see him again here.
- Yeah.
But I'm trying to kind
of think worst-case scenario,
like, okay, he gets a rose.
How does that play out?
- Yeah, I just think
it's kind of...
you know,
prepare for the worst.
But she's a smart woman.
- Yeah.
- And, um, tonight
is his last chance.
And Hannah said last week,
she said,
"Y'all need to trust me."
- Yeah.
- So if--if they grab
his suitcase
and walk out the door--
- We might throw a actual party
here in this house.
- Yeah.
[mellow music]
♪ ♪
- I don't think that there
are any roads that, like,
lead to what I want,
like, what I really want.
Luke, I can't give
you this rose.
- I'm very...
confused right now.
- You know, it took me
literally, like,
raising my voice, like,
so frustrated at you tonight
to get you to just, like,
be the thing
that I think you are.
But, like, as far as today,
we're in the most beautiful
place I've ever been.
- Ever.
- And I was...so frustrated.
And so, like,
I'm not gonna just, like...
Like, going off that,
going off today, like,
absolutely not,
like, 'cause I don't want that.
Like, that wasn't
what I wanted.
- I just--I--I've been really
frustrated today too,
um, really at myself.
- I know, Luke--
- And I feel like nothing
really got anywhere
to the point where we could
be speaking--be, like,
exactly what we wanna be
in today's date.
I feel like--
- But that's what today
was supposed to be about
and we didn't get there,
and that's really frustrating.
- I guess all
I can say is please...
think about everything that
we've talked about tonight.
And...
Everything from day one,
every little detail.
- I'm thinking about
- Like, I am and will be
the first one to say,
"Look, this is my fault."
I screwed up.
My bad.
I'll take full ownership.
Let's move on.
- Giving you a rose tonight,
it doesn't make sense.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- So is this it?
Does that mean
I go home tonight?
♪ ♪
- Yes.
And I just, like,
want you to respect that.
♪ ♪
- [sighs]
- I--
♪ ♪
- I'm pfff--I'm shocked.
Confused.
It never crossed my mind
that I'm gonna go home.
I'm sorry.
♪ ♪
It's a tough pill
to swallow right now.
I didn't ever think this
was gonna happen to me,
but here I am.
♪ ♪
From the moment I met her,
I've felt things
that I've never felt
in my whole entire life.
Our relationship
has been strong,
and our connection
has been strong.
And, really, I--I care
about her so much.
I don't want to go home.
♪ ♪
Hannah was right.
I have tried to be,
quite frankly, perfect.
And now it's like
my eyes have been opened.
♪ ♪
I need to fight for her
because I don't want
to lose her.
Nothing gonna stop me.
Nothing is gonna clutter
or cloud my mind
except pursuing Hannah.
I just see her
and I'm like, "Yes,
"that's what I want,
genuinely,
for the rest of my life."
[door squeaks]
Hannah.
- What are you doing?
- This is my fault,
and I'm sorry.
It's not like I--I didn't
hear you or listen to you.
It's just, I didn't know
what to do
because I didn't know what
emotions I was having.
- Why didn't you address it?
Did you, like--did you
not know there was, like,
something wrong the whole time?
- You know, there was multiple
times where I thought
about stopping you,
and I felt like crying.
I thought a tear was gonna
roll down my face.
Then I felt like screaming,
and then it was like I didn't--
- Well, then scream.
- I didn't know what to do.
- Scream!
- It just--it wasn't--
Nothing was coming out of me.
- I almost had to scream
in your face because
I am going freaking crazy.
And I've screamed about this.
I've cried about this.
And so today, like,
I was just, like,
empty after.
I was like,
"I don't know another way
to say what I need from you."
- Can I stand over here
for a second?
- Why?
- 'Cause I wanna yell.
Like, I seriously, Hannah--
I want to move mountains
for you.
I ha--I--I hate this!
I can't stand it!
Seriously, I cannot stand it.
I--I hate being
in this position.
And, yes, right now, I'm--
I have been freaking out.
Honestly, when you started
this conversation,
I thought you were gonna put
a rose on my--on my coat,
and I understand
why you didn't.
The whole day today,
I feel like--
I feel like I hadn't even
had a day with you yet.
I feel like I've been trying
to explain myself.
Yes, we talked in circles,
and I couldn't stand it.
It--it, like,
was tearing me up.
Like, I'm--I'm so thankful
for this right now.
I feel like you actually get
to see me right now for real.
- I don't...
- I know today sucked,
and I didn't--
I didn't even communicate
with you how I felt.
- I just, like--I--I guess
it's, like, bothering me...
[dramatic music]
'Cause it's, like,
are you taking
what I'm saying seriously?
Because, like,
you didn't understand me.
- I just want you to know
it hasn't hit me till tonight.
No, I--I get it now.
I didn't know how
to describe it.
- Well, say that.
"I don't know
how to describe it."
You were just talking
in circles.
- I felt like--
- And saying the same thing
you've said to me
a zillion times.
- I--I'll admit I--
- And so then do you know
what that means?
It makes it feel not real.
- Yes, I can see that.
I'll admit I froze up
a little bit.
But I just want you
to know that
I am crazy about you and I
feel so strongly about you
and I just--I genuinely
want to marry you.
♪ ♪
And I don't want anything
in the world right now
except you.
I could care less
about anything.
Nothing matters
to me right now
except you.
♪ ♪
And that's seriously
what I want.
- I don't know.
♪ ♪
- I'd be ecstatic if Luke
didn't come home.
- We're all just hoping
for a little peace and quiet,
which is why we want
the guy gone.
- I agree.
- And I'm just hoping I don't
ever see that guy again,
flat out.
I don't need to say bye.
[suspenseful music]
One of two things
is gonna happen:
it's either gonna be a man
coming to get Luke's suitcase,
or it's gonna be Luke
with the rose on.
I think it's pretty obvious
which one we all want.
♪ ♪
[door squeaks]
[clears throat]
- What's up, boys?
She told me that today was
the worst one-on-one she had
throughout this whole process.
And she told me that it was
just frustrating
'cause she felt like we didn't
really get anywhere
trying to talk through things.
But, uh, we did
by the end of the night.
Um, I didn't get a rose.
But Hannah said she still
wants me to be here,
and I'm still here,
so I'm going into
the Rose Ceremony
with you guys.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- The only way I see you
staying here
is bringing up somebody else.
And you said earlier
that you wouldn't do it,
and I hope you didn't do it.
- I didn't.
- Okay.
You realize I don't trust you
when you say that?
- Yeah, I--I--I realize that.
- Okay.
- But I didn't.
I'm still here, so...
- You are.
- If I'm being honest,
I think it's absurd
that we're having to continue
this for another day.
Obviously, she likes you.
It makes my blood boil.
- I mean, she obviously
still wants you here.
The fact that you
didn't get a rose
and you're still here,
I mean,
I think that kinda says a lot.
She's giving you
an opportunity.
- Whether we like you or not,
we want everybody gone
and we wanna be
the last man standing,
but it still doesn't
[indistinct], homie.
And it's hella annoying.
- Just be a man about it, dude.
Just be a man about it
from here on out.
♪ ♪
- I'm pretty aware
that every single guy
doesn't like Luke P.,
but what I did tonight
by not giving him the rose
but not sending him home
was the right decision for me.
And the guys have to trust me
and to know that I'm doing
what's best for my heart,
not just for that relationship
but for all my relationships.
♪ ♪
Finally he was at least meeting
me where I needed him to.
If he continues with the small
moments where he really did
show himself
and show true emotion
and struggle,
then that man
will receive a rose every time.
♪ ♪
But if, by tomorrow, he goes
right back to the weird,
robotic Luke that I have
no connection with,
then he won't get a rose.
- Coming up tonight...
- I am pursuing
my future wife,
so I'm trying
to not screw it up.
- I know Luke P.'s a liar
and I know Luke P.'s
not gonna change,
and I don't want to see Hannah
around somebody like that.
- Hannah loves to do things
her way.
It'll be amazing
if Luke P. goes home.
And tonight,
anything could happen.
- I'm so frustrated.
- The person that's making
her feel bad is Luke.
He likes to win,
no matter what the cost.
- What did you say?
Just what did you say?
- I'm not ever going to lie
to your face.
- Nobody believes you.
- Really?
- Stop.
Please stop.
Everybody thinks it's just
Luke that makes me feel
freaking psycho
and irritated right now.
It's all of you.
[crying]
So I don't wanna do this.
[dramatic music]
[sobbing]
- It's all coming up when
"The Bachelorette" continues.
[tense music]
♪ ♪
- Last night
was eye-opening to me.
[church bells ring]
Hannah is definitely
trying to show me
how serious this is
by not giving me a rose
but yet still keeping me here.
♪ ♪
I feel like she's just
straight-up showing me,
like, "Look,
you're gonna give me
the absolute real Luke,
or you're going home."
And, you know,
I intend on doing that
the rest of my time here.
I am pursuing my future wife,
so I'm trying
to not screw it up.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Going in tonight's
cocktail party,
there's definitely guys
in this house
that I can tell are kind of
pressing and stressing
a little bit about where
their relationship is at
with Hannah at this point,
'cause there are
people that have
strong relationships
in this house.
I have a strong relationship
with Hannah.
You know, at the group date,
we had an amazing time,
and I left that night
with such a high,
and so now it's
to the point just, like,
excited to see her
and get moving.
- Here we go, baby,
game time.
- I had a great time
with Hannah
the last time at the castle.
It was pretty magical,
a night I'll never forget,
and going into tonight,
I have such
a good feeling about us,
and, like, where this can go.
But, at this point,
I really have no idea.
I don't know
where her head's at.
I don't know what's gonna
happen with Luke tonight.
Like, I really don't.
I had a guess last night
if he'd come back
with the rose.
But...no one saw this coming.
He's still here, so there's
a chance for him to get a rose
at the ceremony and, um, we'll
see what happens with that.
- That says a lot
that I'm still here
even though I didn't get
a rose in the one-on-one.
But, you know,
I'm just excited
to make the most
of my time tonight.
- It's a little frustrating
that the guy's
changing this game once again
and, you know, again,
it's all about Luke P.,
but we got
a Rose Ceremony tonight.
You know, two to three people
are going home.
I gotta be aggressive,
and to be aggressive,
it means that, hey,
like, this another chance
to further a relationship
with Hannah.
- There she is.
- Hey.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Sheesh!
- Hi.
- Whoo!
- [giggles]
- You know you look good.
- You look fantastic.
- Thank you.
- Wow.
- You all look great.
Um...
this week has been
a really big week for me.
I feel enlightened
and that my eyes are open.
I know, like,
with some of you,
I've talked about my faith
being important to me.
Um...
but it's really been, like,
what I've held onto
this whole time.
Yesterday, the Lord kind
of placed a verse on my heart
that really just
kind of encompasses
how I feel right now
and hopeful for from all this,
and it was about
"Don't focus on the seen
but on the unseen."
And so I wanna know,
like, what's hard to share
and what makes you you
and your fears
and the hurts that you've had.
I want to have
those conversations,
and to do that, I have
to also get that in return
and get that back.
So cheers to continuing on
in our relationships
and being comfortable
in sharing the uncomfortable.
So cheers.
[laughs]
- Cheers.
[glasses clink]
- Mind if I grab you
for a moment?
- Yeah, let's go.
Tonight I'm yearning for
more in these relationships
because my husband
really could be here,
but it has to progress
to get there,
and I want it to progress
to get there.
- So how's your night going?
- It's going good.
I mean, it just started,
but, like, today more so
it's been, like, really,
like, eye-opening
to, like, what's been
happening, I guess, here.
I just feel like there's
a different, like, feeling
that I'm bringing tonight
to, like, what I want
and, like, what I want to share
so that you guys can.
- It's motivating me
to open up.
It's definitely motivating.
- Well, thank you.
- You know, I appreciate it.
And the other night,
um, I had a great time.
I was out of my element
a little bit,
and, uh, yeah, never worn
a kilt before either,
so that was, uh...
- You looked good.
You did it well.
- Normally,
I wear it on Saturdays,
but, you know, it's--you know,
it was a different day.
- Yeah, settle for
the middle of the week.
- Throw a cog in the wheel
a little bit.
- Yeah.
[laughs]
- No, but I really love
what we talked about.
- Mm-hmm.
- Um...
It felt good
to open that up to you.
- Yeah, well, I think it's
important for you to know,
and this I know--
there's a lot of distractions
and different emotions that go
into it, but I want you to know
that I, like, am really
enjoying getting to know you,
and I'm excited
to continue our relationship
and, like,
want to see what that is,
and that's not coming from
just, like, saying nice things.
I say it, and I mean it.
- I believe you,
and I want you to know that
when I say I'm here for you,
I want you to believe that too.
Took me a little while
to open up a little bit,
but I think we're rolling
pretty steady here now, right?
- Yeah, yeah, I think so,
but, like, I wrote a lot
in my journal, like,
what I wanted and the questions
that I wanted answered about,
like, your past, your present,
like, what
you're struggling with now
and, like, let you know that
that's what I'm looking for
and I can also give.
- I guess that tops off
the bucket now.
It's gonna be flowing, right?
- Yeah.
- I did have a question
for you, though.
It's been weighing on me
a little bit.
- Yeah.
- You know, I apologize
ahead of it, but, um,
so I know you had
a one-on-one with Luke.
- Uh-huh.
- Um, before he left,
I told him,
given what has happened,
to please leave everybody
else's name out of it.
- Mm-hmm.
- And make it about
him and you
and only that.
- Mm-hmm.
- And then when he came back,
I asked him direct in front
of everybody again, "Did you
leave all of us out of it?"
And he said he did.
So I just wanted to see
if he stayed true to his word.
- Yeah, and...
uh...I guess it's important
for me to say, like--
like, I'm aware
that there are feelings
about him from everyone,
and I addressed that.
And so he did say Mike's name.
But I do feel like I provoked
a lot in that moment
and also asked
about another situation,
and he did say Devin and Dylan,
but I think it was just, like,
truly having a conversation
about something, and I
was the one that...asked.
- Thank you. Thank you.
- Yeah.
- Truly.
- Sorry.
- No, no worries.
[overlapping chatter, laughter]
- Oh, my gosh!
- My bad. My bad.
- No, no, you're good.
You're good.
- Mind if I steal her away?
- Go ahead, Connor.
- All right.
- [laughs] Sorry.
- Right now, Hannah and I
have something really good
going on
and it's frustrating, because
I know Luke P.'s a liar
and I know Luke P.'s
not gonna change,
and I don't want to see Hannah
around somebody like that.
- G, what's up?
- Hey, guys.
- Where the hell have you been?
- Yeah, what have you
been doing?
- Floating around, man,
floating around.
- Luke, yesterday,
I did tell you that make sure
no one else's names
come out of your mouth
when you have your
one-on-one with her,
and then when you came back,
I asked you direct
in front of everybody
if anyone's names came out.
- Right.
- And she said that there were
situations
that you brought up
amongst people in the house,
and it was pretty obvious
who you were talking about.
And so she tried to get
the names out of you,
and Mike was a name
that came up.
Um, another situation
was with Dylan and Devin,
and I don't know the manner
the names came up, but--
- What did you say?
- So to be--
- What'd you say, buddy?
- Let me put this glass down.
So to me--
'Cause I told you guys.
Like, I don't ever
want you guys
to feel like I'm talking
about any of you guys
in a negative way and taking up
my time to talk about you guys.
- Dude, what did you say, dude?
Just what did you say?
- Whoa, whoa, whoa,
what'd I tell you--
What'd I ask you
before you left?
- Can I finish real quick?
- What'd I ask you
before you left?
- Can you just let me
finish, please?
- I asked you not
to mention anybody else.
- I will say this: like,
remembering and looking back,
I did bring up Mike's name,
just talking about
how the day went yesterday.
I did talk about Devin.
I talked about
the both of you guys.
- Mm-hmm.
- I didn't say anything
negative or say anything
about your character,
anything like that.
- Luke, no one believes you.
Nobody believes you.
Nobody believes you!
- Really? Can you just be quiet
and let me finish?
- Nobody believes you, dude.
- Connor, I would like
really to talk to you.
I just, like, I'm frustrated.
Just, uh...
[men arguing in background]
[bleep].
So, um,
just give me,
like, a second, okay?
- Yeah. Take your time,
Okay.
- Can you guys not understand
where I'm coming from?
- No.
- Did you say that you swore
that you didn't say
any of our names?
- No, I never said that.
- You didn't say you swore,
or you said you didn't say--
- No.
- Say anybody's names or--
- Take the word
"swore" out of it,
and that is what he said.
- Can you guys not understand
where I'm coming from?
Hannah and I were talking about
we're resolving things that
had been said, conversations
with all of you guys.
- Now, how did that come up?
I just don't--
'Cause
you're on a date, right?
You're on a date with Hannah.
- Yes.
- I'm about to fricking
go in there.
Like, I'm so frustrated.
- But I don't understand how
that conversation comes up.
- You told her that--
- Listen, I appreciate you.
Can I finish, 'cause this is
gonna answer your questions.
- How does that conversation
happen?
- I'm telling you, this is
gonna answer your questions,
I'm telling you, so listen.
- Did you tell her that?
- Did you just say, like,
"Oh, I wanted you to hear..."
- Listen, I appreciate you.
Can I finish?
'Cause this is gonna
answer your questions.
- Did you bring it up?
Did she bring it up?
I don't know she would
have brought it up.
- I'm genuinely
trying to think--
[dramatic music]
- Stop.
I'm so frustrated
about there always
being fights in the house,
and it's pissing me off.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- I don't know
what's going on,
but it's getting
really frustrating
that there are always
being fights in the house.
And then just, like, tell me
exactly what was happening
and I will answer any question
about what he said to me,
and then you can tell me
if that's true or not.
And then we can
all talk about it,
'cause it's affecting
everything, at this point.
- Yeah.
- So ask me.
- Yeah, of course, no, um...
it's, honestly,
very straightforward.
- Can I interrupt you?
- Yeah.
- Hey, let me just explain
to her what's going on here.
- Look, look, you're gonna
have your time tonight.
We're all clearing this up,
right?
- Yeah, yeah, I just want
to talk about what Garrett--
'Cause this is
the most important thing.
This conversation wasn't even
how all this got brought up.
I was manning up to them
because Garrett had asked me
when I left the house--
or, excuse me, got back
from my one-on-one--
- Both.
- Both. He told me,
"Luke, make sure you don't
talk about any of us,"
and I told him, I was like,
"Look, I did bring up
Mike's name."
I think--I don't know
who all I brought up.
I know I brought up
Dylan and Devin
because of that situation
we just talked about.
And I was trying my best
to clear up stuff
that I was trying
to give Hannah clarity.
- Look, I just don't--
Hannah, this is what
I don't understand is...
- Mm-hmm.
- When I'm with you,
I'm focused on us, right?
I'm focused
on our relationship.
So what I'm confused by is
when he's spending time
with you on your one-on-one,
I don't understand
how me and Dylan or Mike
or anybody else comes up.
- 'Cause I am the one
that asked about it.
Going on a one-on-one with him,
I had to clear up what was
happening in the house,
- Of course.
- So that is why
we talked about
other people on our date.
- Of course, that makes sense.
- When I go
on a date with you,
I'm not asking you
what you think about Mike.
- Yeah.
- Because I haven't
heard anything
that's happening.
But because you all have told
me what you thought about him,
I'm gonna ask about
the certain situations
as to why y'all feel that way,
and so that's what I was doing.
- Yeah.
- I'm not trying to
defend him in any way.
Like, I'm aware of some
of the [bleep] he's done.
Like, I--and I've said it
to his face.
But I'm aware that you
don't like him, okay?
And so I'm still trying
to piece it together.
- Gotcha.
- And so I feel bad that
I'm talking about
it one-on-one
right in front of him
to all of you,
but I feel like
it's affecting everything,
so I'm just
gonna clear the air.
I'm tired of hearing
screaming about something--
if you just ask me,
I can tell,
because I'm--obviously,
you don't listen to him,
and hopefully you trust me,
and I'll tell you.
- Of course we--
I think we all trust you.
- So, like, just like with you.
Like, I will tell you
what happened.
And I'm sorry
I just stormed in here,
but I just, like--
could hear the yelling
and, like...
I want to clear everything up
'cause I'm so frustrated.
- I understand that.
- I think everyone got shaken
up because the fact is,
I asked Luke point-blank,
and it's not
any of our business
for you to go in detail,
but you said
you didn't say anything.
- Right.
- Period.
And that's why
we're all confused.
That's why you're getting the
reaction that you're getting,
because--I mean,
what's the point?
I made sure to ask you
before you left
and when you got back
in front of everyone
'cause I wanted
everyone to see.
- Look, the last thing
I want to do
is talk about any
of you guys on this date,
and to me, in my mind--
And I just manned up
and said, "Look, I didn't tell
the truth to you guys,"
'cause when I got back,
I said I didn't bring up
any of your guys' names,
and that is the truth.
But I was looking at it
from, like,
a Luke S. standpoint
of bringing you guys down,
saying anything negative
about you guys,
saying, if--anything, if you're
not here for the right reasons.
- I just don't--
- And I did explain--
Whoa, whoa, let me finish.
- You could've said that, dude.
- Hey, I explained--I just
said that to all of you guys.
- You didn't say that then.
- Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Be real here.
There's haters in the room,
and that's exactly
what I just said to you.
I was explaining situations
'cause there was stuff that
I had to clear up with Hannah.
- Yeah, I get it.
Um...
I wanna continue on
with the night,
but I'm, like,
frustrated as [bleep].
- 100%.
- Um, so...
the thing
I wanna say to you all is,
stay in your freaking lane,
because I'm tired
of hearing screaming.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- Like, honestly,
guys, like, please,
like, can we please
just cut this [bleep]?
Like, I feel like I've just
been, like, not speaking up
or whatever just because
I've been so over this,
but did you just see that?
Like...
[sighs]
How she was?
Like, this sucks.
- She told you,
she's not trying to defend me.
She was explaining
what happened,
And I know that--you know,
not making excuses
in everything that Hannah
was trying to talk to me about,
'cause a lot was on my mind,
but--
Can you just look me
in the eye real quick?
I'm not ever going to lie
to your face intentionally.
Do you understand
where I'm coming from?
- My response is no because
you did not approach me,
and it's the whole--
it's not...
It's not about
what went on, man.
It's the principle of it.
I asked you directly,
"Did you mention anybody else?"
You said, "No."
I said, "Are you sure?"
You said, "Yes."
And that's the thing, man.
It's not--it's not about
what was said.
It was, the fact is
you blatantly lied to--
It wasn't just me,
to everybody.
I said it in front
of everybody for a reason.
- Hey, and I'm--Wait, can
I just say this real quick?
- No, no.
- Wait, wait.
I'm admitting that I did that.
- Wait, wait, wait--
- I'm admitting that.
- And the point is,
if he had not
taken a little bit
of a portion of his one-on-one
time to ask Hannah,
If words or names
were kept out of
from your mouth
that are from her,
you would have just kept that.
- You would have never
said anything, dude.
You're comparing yourself
to Hannah because Hannah...
- Listen.
- Oh, no, you listen, man.
You're comparing yourself
to Hannah.
You didn't do that.
[arguing continues
indistinctly]
[dramatic music]
- [bleep].
Thank you.
I'm so frustrated.
I came in today wanting
to start to open up,
and now I don't at all.
It's all the drama
that is allowing nothing
to get accomplished here.
As far as the end of this,
I don't know what that's
gonna be, because the way
that these guys are fighting,
it is not how a relationship
that is gonna be
sustainable after this
is ever gonna work.
- I didn't even say please.
I said, "Don't mention anybody
else while you're there."
That's it, right?
- Now what I'm trying
to explain to you is...
yeah, I was exhausted,
and, yes--
- Luke, can you just
stop making excuses?
And we've talked about that
because, like, I'm frustrated
and if I'm frustrated,
then I know the whole house is.
Just own up to the things
that you have flaws about
and try to fix those.
But also stop
the focus on him
'cause I can figure that out
for myself...
And focus on me
and know that
I'm a grown-ass woman
and, like, I can decide
if I want to
spend my time figuring
all this out or if I don't.
But you're not
in my conversations with him,
just like he's not in the
conversation with all of you.
So not defending him
in any way,
'cause before any of y'all
brought anything up to me,
there are concerns with him,
but doesn't mean that I don't
have concerns with all of you,
and I'm still giving you
the benefit of the doubt.
So please stop pointing fingers
at other people
and allow me to do that
and focus on yourself
and what maybe I need from you.
I...feel like everybody
thinks it's just Luke
that makes me feel freaking
psycho and irritated right now.
It's all of you.
It's truly all of you
that makes me feel this way.
And although, like,
I came in here, like,
so ready to, like,
to get to know you
and, like, start sharing
things about me
that none of you know.
None of you know
anything about me...
[crying]
and why I'm here
and what makes me me
and things
that I've gone though,
And so, like, I don't feel
comfortable with any of this
'cause nobody's even asked,
'cause all we do is talk
about stupid [bleep].
And so, like, I don't
want to talk to anybody.
[crying]
Because, at this point,
like, I'm just,
like, really defeated
from all of you.
So I don't want to do this.
[poignant music]
[rapidly departing footsteps]
[Hannah sniffling]
[crying]
I'm just so mad.
[sniffles]
- There's no reason
to have, you know,
like, Luke brought up
or this or that.
The fact of the matter is,
she's up here crying,
you know what I mean,
because she can't enjoy herself
here, our last night
in Scotland,
is [bleep] on all of us.
[soft music]
We're messing this up
completely.
♪ ♪
[footsteps]
[tense music]
- I just really am
shocked to see
that we're at this right now
with her feeling like this.
- We were petty, petty fights,
petty arguments.
- Stop being selfish.
Just, like, focus on your
relationship with Hannah
and literally
put everything else to rest.
No more drama.
- I'm sorry I was petty, boys.
I'll admit it.
It sucks admitting it,
but I was petty.
I contributed in this,
and I apologize to all y'all.
I'm gonna apologize to Hannah
when I see her next.
- Hey, Garrett, I will say
I personally
appreciate your apology,
because I had important things
to tell her
and I had important questions
to ask her,
and I wanted to hear things
that she wants to tell me.
And I'm gonna quit
talking about it,
but, hey, I'm--
I'm appreciative
of your apology,
and let's just
stay in our lanes.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- [whimpering]
[sniffles]
[whimpers]
- Hey.
You okay?
- No.
- What's wrong?
- Everything.
- You okay?
- [sobs]
[crying]
- [whispers] Here.
- I'm just, like,
really frustrated 'cause...
[sniffles]
I just, like,
came into here tonight,
like, really, like,
wanting to move forward.
Like, there's other
relationships here
that I really want
to invest time in, but, like,
when the whole thing
is constantly about Luke
in the conversations that
they're having at the house
and I'm having to think
about that,
like, it's taking up
all my time
and not advancing
any of my relationships.
- Yeah. It's because
they're crazy about you.
But so is Luke, and they see
that he's getting
your affection,
your attention,
and it's driving them crazy.
Believe me,
this would be a lot easier
for these guys
if they didn't care.
- Yes, they care,
but they don't respect
or trust me enough
to be able to, like, do this.
- I just wanna make sure
you're okay.
We're all here for you.
It's your party.
- Party's over.
[poignant music]
♪ ♪
- I know I'm in jeopardy.
I hope that she forgives me
for ruining an evening.
That's what I'm scared of.
I feel like tonight
was my fault.
♪ ♪
- This is 100% Garrett's fault.
I did not get a rose
on my one-on-one this week.
I needed to make things right
at the cocktail party,
which was just robbed from me.
And that was like
my last chance.
It sucks,
and I have given Hannah
every right to send me home.
- Hannah's upset
at all of us right now,
so I'm really nervous
for tonight.
I don't know who's going home.
I don't know
what she's gonna do.
[shaky breath]
[someone clears throat]
[tense music]
♪ ♪
Connor.
Connor, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
♪ ♪
- Tyler.
Tyler, will you
accept this rose?
- Always.
♪ ♪
- Dustin?
Dustin, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
♪ ♪
- Peter.
Peter, will you
accept this rose?
- I will.
♪ ♪
- Dylan.
Dylan, will you
accept this rose?
- Of course.
♪ ♪
[dramatic music]
- Garrett.
- [whispers] Excuse me, man.
Thanks.
Garrett, will you
accept this rose?
- Yes, ma'am.
♪ ♪
- Hannah, gentlemen,
this is the final rose
tonight.
When you're ready.
- I think she does
have a plan in this.
Hannah wants to send Luke off
in front of all of us.
She just wants us to see that,
like, she's not playing around.
- It'd be amazing
if Luke P. goes home.
But the fact that she kept him
up until this point,
well, Hannah loves
to do things her way,
and tonight,
anything could happen.
[dramatic, suspenseful music]
♪ ♪
- Luke.
[dramatic musical sting]
Luke, will you
accept this rose?
- With my whole heart.
[soft music]
♪ ♪
- Gentlemen, I'm sorry.
If you did not receive a rose,
take a moment
and say your good-byes.
[low overlapping chatter]
- You're an amazing woman,
and I just want you
to follow your heart.
- Thank you.
- I'm, uh, shocked.
Uh, it's--you know, it's hard.
It's rejection.
She chose Luke P.
That was the last rose.
And, uh...
That is--you know,
that's her choice.
And I'm curious.
I would love to know why.
That would be my only question.
It's like what was
the reasoning behind it?
[emotional music]
No, in fact, I'm just--
I'm perplexed, you know.
I don't know.
- Hi.
Good luck to you.
- Thank you.
- Good luck, Hannah.
I'm just having
to understand a hard time
what she sees
that's so good in Luke P.
I don't know.
Tch.
But ultimately, it's...
it's her decision,
and she made her decision.
- Hey, cutie.
Thank you so much.
It was amazing.
- Thank you.
- The person that's
making her feel bad is Luke,
and it breaks my heart to see
that she likes him that much
that she's not seeing
that he's the issue here.
He likes to win,
no matter what the cost,
and the cost right now
is Hannah's happiness
and sanity, probably.
[somber music]
♪ ♪
- Now we talk.
With everything that happened,
like, I'm just so mad
'cause I know I feel defeated,
uncertain with me
being able to see a future
at the end
of this with anybody.
We have got to all
get on the same page
of how we can do that.
I don't want to feel
the way that I did tonight,
and I'm trying to work through
it, but, like, it's super hard.
Good night.
[dramatic music]
♪ ♪
- You know, I respect
the hell out of her
for saying what
had to be said.
You can't fault her
for that.
- [exhales]
- It just sucks to see her,
like, in that state
and not feel truly confident
that this can work,
because I didn't see very much
hope in her eyes tonight.
I just really hope
that she doesn't
just walk away from all of us.
[dramatic musical sting]
♪ ♪
- Up next...
- Prieka!
- I've never been here before,
so to kind of share it
with Hannah would be great.
- The guys need
to forget the drama
and focus on Hannah.
- I don't know
how this works for people.
- But will it be too little,
too late?
Is it gonna work?
- [inhales]
I don't know.
[dramatic chords]
[upbeat music]
♪ ♪
- Riga.
- Latvia!
- We are in Riga, Latvia,
just south of Estonia
on the Baltic Sea.
This is a beautiful city,
it's super romantic,
and I'm hoping that we left
all that drama in Scotland.
- Wow, this is so cool.
- I thought last week
kind of went up
in unnecessary flames.
I know that there
was some drama.
- Wow, look at this building.
- Whoo!
- And I hated to see
Hannah upset.
It really upsets me,
and I wanna be there for her,
and I don't wanna
see that again.
- Whoa, what is that?
- I'm just excited to get
to see Hannah this week.
I want her to be happy.
- Prieka to Latvia.
- Prieka.
- I think Hannah might
have a few doubts
in the back of her mind
just because
it's been a rough week.
I realized last night
that even though I felt
like I made the right move,
it was still a move based off
a distraction, and I needed
to put all that distraction
to the side
and focus on Hannah.
- I've never been here before,
so to kind of share it
with Hannah would be great.
- I hope I never see Hannah
that upset ever again.
[bell tolling]
- I honestly
just want to make sure
you're doing okay
in all this,
'cause Scotland
got a little rough.
- I'm like, "Can I just
have one...cocktail party
that doesn't
go to crap by the end?"
It's very frustrating.
Every week has been...
Ridiculous.
- I just don't want you
to have another week
where it's like,
"Well, there was Rhode Island,
"there was Scotland,
there was Latvia,
and now they all kind of
run together."
At some point,
I want you to be like...
[clicks tongue]
"Latvia, that was
the turning point.
"That's where...you know,
got some wind in my sails
and I started to really
dive into these relationships."
- I think when
I'm with each man in this,
like, I definitely am,
like, completely in it
unless they don't
allow me to be.
I'm not trusting
these relationships
as much as I want to,
and I feel like I'm getting
nowhere because I haven't felt
like these men are ready
to know exactly who I am yet.
I just want to feel like I can
share with somebody,
and I'm not gonna do it
unless I feel led to share,
and I haven't felt led to share
'cause I haven't been
asked the questions, so...
- These guys gotta pick it up
a little bit.
- Yeah, for sure.
- Earn it.
- I just, like...
Need it to change.
- I mean,
are you still hopeful?
- [sighs]
I'm trying to stay hopeful.
I hate that I'm having to try.
That's--that's what I--
It's like, "Why do you have
to try so hard?"
- What do you feel like
you're trying?
- I don't know exactly how
to answer that.
Um...
To just, like,
not want to give up.
I don't...
[inhales]
[sighs]
I don't know.
- It feels heavy.
- Yep.
Feel very weighted down.
[somber music]
- There's been a lot of drama.
I understand the emotional toll
that takes.
- Um...
I thought--no, definitely not
how I anticipated it going.
I thought I would have more
of a understanding by now
of my feelings and emotions.
So...
like, I'm kind of flailing.
♪ ♪
And, like, I asked for a lot,
like, from everyone
and I expect a lot
out of a relationship
but I don't want to settle.
- Nor should you.
- I just don't want
to give my heart
to anybody
that doesn't deserve it too.
If my husband's not here, like,
I don't want to have given
everything of me away.
- I get that,
but I feel like
you're fighting it
a little bit.
- In the past, I have given it
to other people
that I thought were
gonna be my husband,
and then I was--
been damaged for...
years, and I'm finally, like,
getting myself back together,
and I don't wanna
go through that again.
- Well, my hope is
we turn this thing around...
And that you end up
with someone you truly love
and who loves you,
and I don't think that--
I don't think that's lost yet.
- I don't know.
I don't know how this works
for people.
I thought I did.
I thought it did work.
[inhales]
- Is it gonna work?
- I don't know.
I don't know.
[sniffles]
I don't know
if it's gonna work anymore.
[sniffling]
[dramatic musical flourish]
- Up next...
- I put everything into this,
and it's just completely
trampled over by stupid drama.
- I've been
nothing but truthful,
and you are not
gonna mess it up!
- Has Hannah lost all hope?
- [crying]
I don't know if I can see it.
Get away from me.
- It's all coming up when
"The Bachelorette" continues.
[solemn music]
♪ ♪
- Good evening.
Our bachelorette
is going through
one of the most
difficult times in her life.
As we all just found out,
Hannah doesn't know if
she'll be able to fall in love
with any of the remaining men.
When I spoke with her
in Latvia,
it wasn't even clear to me
if she wanted
to continue at all.
So how did we
get to this point?
What happened
that made Hannah talk about
giving up on her dream
of finding love?
I know this might seem
a little unusual,
but it's important to address
these serious questions
about the future of the show
before Hannah's journey
can continue.
So I sat down with her
to get to the bottom of it.
Thanks for
sitting down with me.
Uh, I think there are
some things
we need to get
to the bottom of...
- Yeah.
- Most importantly,
your feeling that
this can't work for you.
- I knew it was gonna be
difficult.
And I knew there would be
a lot of emotions involved,
but I didn't realize how hard
this whole journey
would be for me.
And...
I don't see, at this point,
how I'm gonna get to where
I need to be at the end.
- You said something very
telling to me the other day.
You said, "I don't know
how this works for anybody.
I don't know
how this has ever worked."
- Yeah.
Um...
- How did we get to that point?
- It's all been building up.
- Mm-hmm.
- From the beginning of this,
I've put so--
I've put everything into it,
into making sure that
I could go all in.
And it's just getting
completely trampled over
by stupid drama.
- Yeah.
Well, I think in order
to figure this out,
let's first remember
how we got to this point.
The drama started night one.
- Yeah.
Hey, Scott.
We need to talk.
- Okay.
- Yeah.
Come on.
It was super frustrating
from the very first night
having Scott
have other intentions.
You have a girlfriend.
- Ooh.
- Yes, I was dating a girl
before I got on the show,
up until Monday, if you want me
to be completely honest.
Yes, up until Monday.
- You have another girl at home
that you still have
on the line,
and that is [bleep].
And so you know what?
I'm done with this.
So let's go.
- That guy sucks.
Seriously, like,
don't come
here if you have a girlfriend.
- This thing started with
a guy like Scott
wasting your time.
- It's a slap in the face
for me,
because I'm investing my whole
life and future into this
for somebody who just honestly
has no respect
for himself or me.
- So Scott wasn't the only one
who brought drama early on.
- No.
- There's something
very, very personal
and very serious in my life
that I need to
discuss with Hannah,
so I need to just
pull her aside for a second.
- Cam had got in his head
that he was going home,
that he needed a rose.
So he needed to basically
his Hail Mary.
- I got a call from my dad that
my grandma had passed away.
- The pity rose.
- The most recent surgery
that I had
in November of 2017
hit me the hardest,
because I actually had
a ten-month-old puppy
at the time
that I was super close to
that I had to rehome.
- Girl don't give out
pity roses.
So that--that did not fly
with me.
I just feel like
it's an interesting time
for you
to bring up this story.
This just feels really schemy
and slimy to me.
- Why are we giving Cam
so much [bleep] time?
- We can't have one person just
sap up our day with Hannah.
- I mean, Hannah knows all the
stuff that Cam's pulled, right?
- Don't get me wrong.
I'm--I'm really thankful
for any guy
sharing something
really vulnerable with me.
- Right.
- But do it because you want
to share it with me,
not because you feel like
you have to to save yourself.
- Right.
Okay, so that brings us
to the guy
who stirred up the most drama.
- Okay.
- Luke.
- [laughs]
Luke P.
- Hannah,
I'm genuinely starting
to fall in love with you.
[cheers and applause]
- Who, on the very first date
of the season,
professed his love for you.
But the guys don't love it.
- I understand it, 'cause
I have a relationship
with him.
But it didn't need to be
shared with everyone.
[cheers and applause]
Luke has a tendency to make
group dates like one-on-ones,
and it was starting to affect
me with my other relationships.
- How you doing?
- Good.
Can I have, like,
just a few more minutes?
We're talking about something.
- You guys almost wrapped up?
- It's kind of personal, yeah.
- It puts me
in a really bad situation,
and I can feel the tension
from the other guys.
- You put him in check.
- Well, yeah.
- You put him in his place.
- I promise I'm gonna
talk to you again.
But, like, I want to, like,
call my own shots.
He's not the only one here.
And, like, buddy,
slow your roll.
[cheers and applause]
- And then things really came
to a head on the rugby date
in Rhode Island.
- [screams]
- Luke's obviously
a very competitive guy.
But Luke S. and Luke P.
made a play.
- Hey!
[men grunting]
[crowd screams]
- I just saw, like, them
kind of on the ground.
- What did he just do?
- He body slammed Luke S.
and dropped a knee
on the guy's head?
- That's really
where I feel like
everything just started
coming to a head.
- You kneed my partner
in the face while he was down.
You can't even do that
in the UFC.
- I did not!
- You, time and time again,
are the issue.
You're unstable.
You are a psychopath.
That's who you are.
- And at one point
at the Rose Ceremony,
you're sitting
between the two Lukes
as they're yelling
at each other.
- The Luke feud.
- Luke, you made up
a bald-faced lie about me.
You then go to her
and say that I forced you
to basically go talk to her.
- Did you or did you not...
- I said to you...
- Tell me, "Will you go
talk to Hannah about me?"
- I said, "Go tell her the
truth and say that you lied."
Because it's the truth,
and you are a liar.
- You would think
that they would, like,
settle down
'cause I'm in the room.
- Right.
- No. Went after it.
- It was like
you weren't even there.
- It was--
I wasn't there.
But I thought maybe after that,
like, after Luke S. is gone,
like, surely,
Scotland, we'll start anew.
And--
[sighs]
- Man, it didn't.
- No.
- I told Hannah that I thought
Luke wasn't here
for all the right reasons.
- Why did you say
that he wasn't here
for the right reason,
though?
- You smeared him.
You smeared him.
- You're a liar.
- I understand, but--
- No, I'm not.
- Here's my--
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Just don't cross the line
anymore.
- I felt like everything
was going wrong.
How it just seemed like
the whole house was in--
like with the drama, and
it really started affecting me.
Hearing you say, like,
you don't, you know,
have any worries
about our relationship;
I definit--I do.
Luke, I can't give you this
rose.
It was like, "How is one guy,
like, completely
destroying this for me?"
- Right.
- But I wasn't ready to,
like, let go.
- I didn't get a rose.
But Hannah said she still
wants me to be here.
And I'm still here.
So I'm going into the Rose
Ceremony with you guys.
- And then the cocktail party.
Or attempt.
It just disintegrated.
- I'm not ever going to lie
to your face.
- Luke, no one believes you.
Nobody believes you.
- Really? Can you just be
quiet and let me finish?
- My intentions going into
the night were so pure,
and it all got crushed
in an instant
by, yet again,
drama in the house.
- I'm admitting
that I did that.
I'm admitting that.
- That was just
where I just exploded
and I was just done.
Stop.
Please stop.
I feel like everybody
thinks it's just Luke
that makes me feel
freaking psycho
and irritated right now.
It's all of you.
Stop the focus on him,
'cause I can figure that out
for myself.
None of you know
anything about me
and why I'm here...
[sniffling]
And what makes me me and things
that I've gone through.
'Cause all we do is talk about
stupid [bleep].
Like, I'm just, like,
really defeated
from all of you.
So, like, I don't want to do
this.
It was like the--
the last straw for me.
- Yeah.
- Like, I just--
LA, Rhode Island, Scotland.
Like, I was just can't get
past it.
And I was just done.
If it's--if it continues
to be a...
an obstacle, like...
I don't see
this working for me.
But if I can get past this,
I still have a glimmer of hope.
[soft music]
- He has a ring in his pocket
right now.
He is ready to propose to you.
Has Hannah reached
the end of the road?
He went out and got a ring.
He demanded to see you.
He is fully convinced
that you are his wife.
- [sobbing]
I don't know what to do.
And I'm scared.
- When "The Bachelorette"
continues.
[solemn music]
- It really has been
a drama-filled season.
Yeah, I always say
it's the most dramatic.
This is the most drama-filled
we've ever had.
- Yeah.
- But let's move on
from the drama.
Let's talk about
some good stuff.
Some of your favorite moments,
some of your favorite dates.
- Yeah.
- What's been your favorite
date so far?
- [sighs]
So hard.
I really like
my very first date.
- Whoo!
[cheers and applause]
I loved the Mr. Right Pageant.
- Yeah.
- It was like bringing the guys
into my world,
but then with
some fabulous drag queens.
- Hi!
- Hello.
- That I got to hang out with
all day.
So...really fun.
[cheers and applause]
It was cool to see the guys
go out of their comfort zone
for me,
and then actually, I think,
have a really good time.
Yeah!
Pa-pow!
- During that date,
Jed brought the house down.
- ♪ I'll be your Mr. Right ♪
♪ Girl ♪
♪ Ooh-ooh ♪
- He killed it with that song.
- Killed it.
[light guitar music]
[high voice]
- ♪ I'll be your Mr. Right ♪
[cheers and applause]
- He handles things well.
- Yeah.
- Remember when he walked in
on you and Luke in the massage?
- [sighs]
Oh, my God.
[both laughing]
- You're so cute.
- What's going on?
- [laughing]
Uh, massages,
actually.
- Oh.
- I know this is not
what you wanted
to see right now.
- Yeah, man.
- It's not what it looks like.
I promise.
- It was so bad, so awkward.
He could have been like,
"Why am I even here?"
Like, "What was that?"
But I think he could tell that
it really bothered me.
This is just freakin' weird.
- I should have, like, walked
back in with my pants off.
- [laughs]
Yes.
- Yeah, yeah.
"If we're massaging"...
- I would have died.
He made the choice
to let it go
so that our relationship could
move forward and progress.
- I feel something
growing inside of me
that I've never felt before.
I'm starting to feel like I'm
falling for you more and more.
- He is very in tune
with what I need.
I like that guy.
- All right.
So you were able to have fun
with some of the guys,
despite all the drama
that was going on.
- Yeah.
- We would like you
to experience
the true joy of childbirth
with this labor simulator.
- Oh.
[men groan]
- I think you're
the first bachelorette
to ever put your men
through a crash course
in labor and delivery.
- Now here we go.
The baby's coming.
- [groans]
Oh!
[both groaning]
- Oh, God!
- It's okay. It's okay.
They can at least say
I feel your pain,
because they have felt it.
- Oh!
[laughter]
- John Paul Jones, especially.
- Oh, my gosh.
John Paul Jones.
- Don't do it.
Don't do it.
- It isn't even on.
- Which is funny, 'cause he's
the most chill dude.
- Not then.
You gotta look at me.
- [screaming]
[bleep]!
- Okay.
- Oh, my God.
[laughter,
both screaming]
- I think someone even screamed
out my name during labor.
- Mike, yes.
- Big Mike.
- Oh-ho-ho-ho.
- Breathe...okay.
- Oh, Chris Harrison.
[laughter]
- I feel like Mike just brings,
like, joy wherever he is.
And I love that.
- I'm 31 years old.
I've learned a lot of things
in my life.
And I truly know who I am and
what I want.
I'm really ready.
I'm really, really ready.
I can see myself getting down
on one knee
in a few weeks,
if I'm ever so lucky.
- Thank you.
He pushes me
to open up to him so that
he can get to know me
on a more intimate level.
- I'm gonna pick you up.
[both laughing]
- That's what I want
from somebody,
and he definitely
does that.
- You and Mike connected
in Scotland...
- Yeah.
- But there were other guys
that put up a good fight
for you there too.
[crowd cheering]
- [screams]
- You put the guys in kilts.
- Yes.
[men grunting]
- Did you catch a glimpse
of anything?
- I saw a few boulders.
[laughing]
- What happens in a kilt
doesn't stay in a kilt.
- [laughs]
And so I know.
- How are you?
- You're working that kilt.
How's it feel?
- Good.
You know, I saw you creeping,
so I brought it back
in case you wanted to
take another peek,
you know what I mean?
If there's anything you want
to see, speak up, you know?
- Okay, okay.
- Another guy you seem to have
chemistry with is Tyler C.
- Man, that boy
is good-looking.
Dang.
- Ooh.
- [laughs]
- He also really helped you
through a tough time.
- Yeah.
I could not shake
how the Luke S.,
Luke P. situation
was going down,
so I was really heavy
and just needed somebody
to just hold me.
I know I'm supposed to be here,
but sometimes I'm like
I don't know why
and if it's gonna work.
- Come here.
I'm here for you.
- The moments
where he just sat with me
and allowed me
to just, like, be
really showed me
that there was so much more
with our relationship
than just physical.
There are not many people
that could have
made me feel comforted today.
I'm thankful for you.
- I'm glad I could be that guy.
- I don't think that morning
I could have ever imagined
feeling the way I did.
It ended up being
a really good date.
- He turned you around.
- Yeah.
- Another guy we have to
talk about:
Peter.
- Yeah, Peter.
- I'm just so happy to be here.
- I'm glad that you're here
too.
- So I had a question.
Now, you, um...
are your bags packed?
'Cause I got the jet
waiting outside, so--
- [laughs]
Yeah, let's go.
Where are we going?
- Okay, well, you tell me.
- Somewhere warm.
- I'm your pilot, so,
somewhere warm--I can do that.
- He kind of snuck up on you.
- Definitely.
I just thought Peter was sweet.
Didn't really know
where he fell in the pack.
- So I wanted to, like,
officially ask
if you wanted to
be my girlfriend.
I know--
- Oh, my gosh.
- I'll preface it with
I'm okay with you dating,
like, 14 other guys
at the same time.
- I would love
to be your girlfriend.
- Would you?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
- Man.
- For someone who
really started off slow,
he's come on strong.
- Yeah.
Boy, did I see more of him.
I mean...
- [laughs]
Pinned me up against a wall.
- Oh, my God.
- Whoo!
- Good move?
- Whew!
Great move.
[laughs]
- Okay, before you became
the bachelorette,
you told me you'd only kissed,
like, four or five guys...
- Five. Yeah.
- Your entire life.
- Yeah.
- Really only five guys...
- Only five.
- Before "The Bachelorette"?
- Promise.
- You've been
the kissing bandit.
- [sighs]
- Okay, be honest.
Who's the best kisser?
It's not that hard
of a question.
- No, yes, it is,
because they're all different.
- But who's that one
where you're like,
"Okay, I could
just make out all day"?
- Luke.
[laughs]
- Overall, despite some drama,
you really gotta be happy
with the group of guys
that are here
to win your heart.
- I am.
I have a heck of
a group of guys.
- You got your work
cut out for you.
- I definitely have
my work cut out for me.
And...
[sighs]
Gah.
If I survive,
at the end of this,
somebody buy me a drink.
Could you buy me a drink,
you think?
- Hopefully you'll have a man
to do that by then.
- Yeah.
- At the beginning
of this night,
you were really feeling
that this can't work for you.
- Mm-hmm.
- Okay.
Well, we've seen
a lot of your journey so far.
I want to find out
how you're doing now.
- Okay.
- But before we do,
let's talk about some moments
that not everybody's
had a chance to see--
not even you.
[both mimicking
electric guitars]
- Then you shred.
Zzz!
Pow, pow, pow!
And then you throw the guitar.
And you go, "Yeah!"
- Whoo!
[fabric rips]
- Oh!
- [laughs] Oh, wow.
- Did you rip your pants?
Did you really rip 'em?
[gasps] He really--
[both laughing]
[laughs]
- And that wasn't
the only awkward moment
the audience
didn't get a chance to see.
- For sure.
- You had a date in Boston.
You and Jed are there.
You're excited,
having some ice cream...
- Oh, hello.
- And someone shows up.
- Hi.
- What's your name?
Penny!
- Oh.
- Penny.
- Penny's in heaven right now.
He's, like, in there,
anywhere I go.
- [laughs]
- [barks]
- He went to town on it.
- Yeah, that's awkward.
- All right.
Bye, Penny.
- Bye, Penny.
All right.
- I know, it's too good
to resist.
- I'm gonna get
back in here now.
- [laughs]
No!
- What was
either the most awkward
or the weirdest moment
you had with one of the guys?
- Oh, God.
Jonathan.
- Oh, yeah?
- [laughs]
He went in for a kiss, and...
- What happened?
- Oh, God, it was so bad.
We were sitting right here.
- Yeah?
- I'm actually very excited
to share this moment with you,
honestly.
You know, I'm a man of passion.
One thing I am very passionate
about is basketball.
I do--
I know.
I do--I mean, I actually
made this myself.
- He started talking
about this basketball,
but I could tell,
like, he wanted to kiss me.
- I, uh...
I'm always willing
to shoot my shot,
and, um...
I feel like now just might be
my perfect time.
[light music]
Yeah, so...
if, uh--if you're willing
to take that chance with me,
I'd be more than willing
to do that.
- Absolutely.
- Excellent.
- So...
[murmurs]
- He went in for a kiss,
and I kind of side--
- He got cheek?
- It was so awkward.
It's very obvious when I want
someone to kiss me.
- Oh, of course.
Body language.
- I'm leaning in.
- You lean in--yeah, no, it's--
Read the body language, boys.
If you don't know,
then don't go.
- The ball's in your court.
- Ball's in my court now.
- Ball's in your court, okay?
Throw right here.
Ooh!
- Oh, I hit your face.
- That's okay.
It's fine.
A little kiss will make it
all better.
- [smooches]
- [laughs]
- It was bad.
Like, I--he walked off,
and I was like,
"Oh, God.
That was bad."
[both laugh]
- But you had a few unseen
awkward moments yourself.
You had an unexpected visitor,
night one, here at the mansion.
His name: Marcus.
- [laughs]
I went to go powder my face
and then realized that, uh...
there was this monstrosity
on my cheek
that just developed overnight.
And, um...
Marcus was the name
I gave my pimple.
- Why did you name
the zit on your face Marcus?
- Going into the first night,
I don't know
any of these guys' names.
- Right.
- And I would make up names:
Jim Bob and Marcus.
Marcus is like the guy that
keeps butting in
on the conversations.
- Right.
Can I steal you for a moment?
- You didn't want to be Marcus.
And when I started getting
this little friend on my face,
I named it Marcus.
Nobody likes a Marcus.
Nobody
likes a Marcus.
- But here's the best part
about Marcus.
'Cause apparently he really got
deep into your heart.
- Is everybody in here?
- Because when you
sent Scott home,
[laughing]
you called him Marcus.
- So Marcus
is a piece of [bleep].
He had a girlfriend back home.
So, uh--
- Scott?
- Scott.
[laughter]
- And the guys are like,
"Uh, who's Marcus?"
- Is there even a Marcus here?
- [softly]
Why did I say Marcus?
I'm glad that Marcus is gone
but not forgotten.
- All right, you came into
tonight ready to quit,
reached your limit.
Where do we go from here?
- I don't know.
It's...been really tough.
And because of the drama,
I have pulled back
and retreated.
And I really need to
reevaluate all this.
- What are you afraid of?
- Just not being able to
invest in a relationship
that really needs--
that really could be it
and not being able to do that
just because of how
my heart operates
and how I have to go all in.
And it's hard to allow myself
to because of the drama.
- Do you think
you'll get there?
- I don't know if I will,
to be completely honest.
I--I would love to.
Because I want to be able
to fall in love.
And I see that there are
relationships here
that, like,
really could be it for me.
But I--
I'm not gonna settle
and just go into something
if it's not
where it needs to be.
- So I guess the most important
thing is,
do you want to continue?
- [sighs]
I have really
lost a lot of hope,
but I'm still holding on to
to knowing that there's gotta
be good that comes out of this.
It's hard, but...
I--
I don't give up.
- I wouldn't expect you to.
- Nope.
I'm gonna complain about it,
because I gotta be loud
and be real about
exactly how I feel
and go through
all the emotions,
but I'm gonna see this thing
through to the end.
- Well, I wish you
the very best.
And I truly appreciate
you sitting down with me.
- Thank you.
It's always a pleasure.
- Up next...
[dramatic music]
- Get away from me.
- What happens next
for Hannah?
- I'm so freaking nervous.
I don't know if I can see it
just yet.
- Find out
with a dramatic sneak peek
at the rest of the season.
He has a ring in his pocket
right now.
He is ready to propose to you.
- [sniffles]
Things would have been so
different if he wasn't here.
- This is gonna change
everything.
- [sobs]
- That's coming up right now
when "The Bachelorette"
continues.
- And now,
it's a special sneak peek
at the rest of the season.
- It has been
a wild ride today.
My body on her body.
Things have heated up.
That's for sure.
I need to cool myself down,
man.
- Whoo!
I am loving this.
- Love is definitely
in the air,
and we're right there
on the same page.
- I felt that spark
and that connection.
I knew
I was falling in love.
- We burnt it down
with our fire.
- Ooh!
- [laughs]
I want to be physical
with him.
But I don't want to
just have sex.
I want to, like,
love you in every way.
Do you want to kiss me?
- Yes.
I'm completely,
madly in love with her,
and I can't wait
to have sex with her
when we're married.
- Our physical connection
is a ten out of ten.
And hopefully
I'm gonna get down...
[mimics sultry music]
Ow!
♪ In the fantasy suite ♪
[both screaming]
- Hannah went bungee jumping
naked with Garrett.
That's like
a slap in the face
from her and from Garrett.
I don't even want to talk to
you guys right now.
I have a lot to think about
between me and Hannah.
- Where I'm from,
we call that [bleep].
- I want to make sure that...
[laughs]
she's not sleeping around.
I don't--I don't think
she would ever do that,
but yeah, I gotta--
I gotta make sure.
- I just don't fully
understand
how you can be as
amazing as you are
and you can consider
someone like him.
- I'm so freaking nervous.
I don't know if I can see it
just yet.
- I don't care
what you said to her.
I've been nothing but truthful,
and you are not
gonna mess it up!
- There have been some people
questioning Hannah.
It sucks that we're
in this position yet again,
and it's because of Luke P.
[thunder claps]
- So let's talk about sex.
- Okay.
- And how the marriage bed
should be kept pure.
And let's say you have had sex
with one or multiple
of these guys.
I'd be wanting to go home.
- You don't get to decide
what I can and can't do,
because you don't own me.
Oh, my God, I cannot believe
you just said that.
I'm so mad.
I don't owe you anything.
Get the [bleep] away from me.
My husband would never say
what you said to me.
I believe that sex was made
for a man and a woman
in marriage,
but I am having physical
relationships.
So, like, I have had sex.
- [groans]
- And honestly,
Jesus still loves me.
The Lord made sex
to be amazing,
and guess what.
A man does not control
anything that I do.
This is my decision.
- This is gonna
change everything,
because he went out
and got a ring.
He demanded to see you.
He is fully convinced
that you are his wife,
that you are the one.
He has a ring in his pocket
right now.
- What?
- He is ready
to propose to you.
- [sobbing]
I'm obviously struggling.
[sobbing]
Things would have been
so different
if he wasn't here right now.
I don't know what to do,
and I'm scared.
[sobbing]
- Hannah's shocking journey
to find love
continues next week
on "The Bachelorette."
- I think Riga
is a beautiful city.
It's home to many
beautiful creatures.
[birds chirping]
But there's
so much distraction here
with all these birds.
[pigeons cooing]
It is really just symbolic
of the distractions
in my relationships.
Stop all your cooing
and cawing,
and mate already.
Men, stop all your cooing
and cawing,
and try to mate with me.
[crow caws]
Hey, oh...
[laughs]
is my mating call.
[squawking]
[pigeon cooing]
- [laughing]
Ahh!
[screams]
[laughing]
Sorry about that.
I just had some business
to take care of.